PUNITA SHAH

TEAM LEAD (IT SUPPORT AND OPERATIONS)



CONTACTS

+91-97730 20235

shahpunita84@gmail.com

10, Navjivan Park, Near
Thakorji Nagar, Civil Hospital
Road, Nanakwada, Valsad,
396 001, Gujarat, India.

SKILLS

- Application Support
- Production Support
- JIRA
- AWS-CloudWatch
- ServiceNow
- ActiveCollab
- Problem Solving
- Client Communication

LANGUAGES

- English
- Gujarati
- Hindi

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth

23/01/1984

Nationality

Indian

Marital status

Single

ABOUT ME

5 Years of Experience of working as Team Lead of Application Support and Operatins Team.

Interested in similar kind of Roles as well as seeking for any challenging opportunity in QA/BA or Data Analysis in reputed IT Firm.

Ready to relocate anywhere in India.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Team Lead - Web Grabbing Support & Operations, Emsure Limited, SURAT

Jan 2020 - Present

Client - Thomson Reuters, London.

Roles and Responsibilities:

Responsible for End to End Support Services to the News & Editorial Bureau of Thomson Reuters.

- · Defect Management and Resolution using JIRA.
- · Case and Incident Management using Service Now.
- Business Process Improvement using AWS Cloud-Watch.

Overall Team Management Including -

- · Shift Scheduling, Task Allocation, Reviewing, Taking Follow up,
- · Service Delivery,
- · Client Meetings,
- · Issue Resolution,
- Strategic Planning.

Team Lead - Web Grabbing Support & Operations, Varee Infotech, SURAT

Oct 2016 - Dec 2019

Client - Thomson Reuters, London.

Roles and Responsibilities: Same as Emsure Limited.

Business Analyst, DRC Infotech, SURAT

Dec 2015 - Apr 2016

Clients: Various Diamond Firms of Surat.

Business Domain: CMS and E-Commerce Websites and Mobile Apps for the Diamond Industries.

Platforms: Wordpress, Magento, Core PHP, Open-Cart, Shopify.

Roles and Responsibilities:

End to End Client Communications,

Requirement Gathering,

Involvement with Development Team for distinct phases of SDLC,

Involvement in Client Testing and approval.

Visiting Lecturer / Assistant Professor, Govt. Collage of Engineering, VALSAD Sep 2009 - Aug 2010

1 Year of Academic Experience of teaching following subjects to First Year Engineering students.

C++,

Data Structures,

Number Systems,

EDUCATION

M.C.A., Veer Narmad South Gujarat University, SURAT

2009

B.Sc. (Mathematics), Veer Narmad South Gujarat University, SURAT 2006

COURSE

DST (Diploma in Software Testing), Seed Infotech, Pune.

Apr 2013 - May 2014